

Profile

Graphic designer with +9 years of experience in digital & traditional marketing. Skilled at content creation, as well as branding & photography. Has a history with a range of clients including dentists, gas stations, hospitals, lawyers, restaurants, retail, & grocery stores.

Main Skills

- Active Campaign
- Facebook
- FIGMA
- Google
- Illustrator
- MailChimp
- Photoshop

Contact Information

Tel: 478-719-0474

Email: j.m.howard30@gmail.con

Location: Macon, GA

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/jenna-howard

Employment

Marketing Specialist at SPINEN

2020 - 2023

Translated ideas into concrete design for clients & internal staff. Developed promotional materials including brochures, clothing, manuals, .pdfs, pens, power points, signage, & social media posts. Managed social media pages & client interaction. Implemented digital ads that reached >30k people & newsletters that earned >\$30k in revenue.

Graphic Designer at Freelance

2019-2023

Overhauled client branding & content planning. Constructed & maintained client web pages, Google Business pages, & social media accounts. Started mailing list for customer newsletters. Produced menus, photo shoots, & advertising for holiday catering. Reported client analytics.

Education

Georgia College & State University

2011-2015

Bachelor of Arts in Mass Communication